(Missy:)Any news you want me
to pass along to Mom?
(Sheldon:)Well, she might be interested to know
that I've refocused my research...
(Sheldon:)...from bosonic string theory
to heterotic string theory.
Yeah, I'll just tell her you said, "Hey."
(Sheldon:)Okay. Well, it was pleasant seeing you.
(Sheldon:)Other than that business
with my testicles.
(Howard:)Come on, Shelly.
(Missy:)I want you to know
I'm very proud of you.
(Missy(who has just entered):)- Really?
- Yep.
(Missy:)I'm always bragging to my friends
about my brother, the rocket scientist.
(Sheldon:)You tell people I'm a rocket scientist?
- Well, yeah.
- I'm a theoretical physicist.
- What's the difference?
- Goodbye, Shelly.
- My God.
Why don't you just tell them that
I'm a toll taker at the Golden Gate Bridge?
A rocket scientist, how humiliating.